<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<text name="DataRilascio" extra="true">
			<text>1978</text>
		</text>
		<text name="Produttore" extra="true">
			<text>APF Electronics</text>
		</text>
		<text name="nomesistema_nu" extra="true">
			<text>M-1000</text>
		</text>
		<text name="Descrizione" extra="true">
			<text>The APF Microcomputer System is a second generation 8-bit cartridge-based home video game console released in October 1978 by APF Electronics Inc. with six cartridges. The console is often referred to M-1000 or MP-1000, which are the two model numbers of the console. The APF-MP1000 comes built-in with the game Rocket Patrol. The APF-MP1000 is a part of the APF Imagination Machine.
It is the successor to the APF TV Fun line of first generation consoles.</text>
			<text lang="pl">APF Microcomputer System to 8-bitowa domowa konsola do gier wideo drugiej generacji, wydana w październiku 1978 roku przez APF Electronics Inc. z sześcioma kartridżami. Konsola jest często określana jako M-1000 lub MP-1000, które są dwoma numerami modelu konsoli. Do konsoli APF-MP1000 dołączona jest gra Rocket Patrol. APF-MP1000 jest częścią APF Imagination Machine.
Jest następcą linii konsol APF TV Fun pierwszej generacji.</text>
			<text lang="ru">Игровая приставка второго поколения, представляет собой 8-битную домашнюю игровую приставку.
Является преемником линейки консолей APF TV Fun, относящихся к первому поколению. Выпущена в октябре 1978 компанией APF Electronics Inc. с шестью игровыми картриджами. Устройство упоминается как M-1000 или MP-1000, поскольку это номера модели консоли.</text>
			<text lang="it">L'APF Microcomputer System è una console per videogiochi domestici a 8 bit di seconda generazione, rilasciata nell'ottobre 1978 da APF Electronics Inc. con sei cartucce. La console viene spesso indicata come M-1000 o MP-1000, che sono i due numeri di modello della console. L'APF-MP1000 veniva fornito con il gioco Rocket Patrol. L'APF-MP1000 fa parte della APF Imagination Machine.
È il successore della linea di console APF TV Fun di prima generazione.</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
