<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<text name="DataRilascio" extra="true">
			<text>2008</text>
		</text>
		<text name="nomesistema_nu" extra="true">
			<text>LÖVE</text>
		</text>
		<text name="Descrizione" extra="true">
			<text>LÖVE (or Love2D) is an open-source cross-platform engine for developing 2D video games. The engine is written in C++ and uses Lua as its scripting language. It is published under the zlib license.
The API provided by the engine gives access to the video and sound functions of the host machine through the libraries SDL and OpenGL, or since version 0.10 also OpenGL ES 2 and 3. Fonts can be rendered by the FreeType engine.
It also provides a basic "sandbox" management of the files in order to avoid giving access to all its disk to the executed games.
In July 2018, it was the 10th game engine most used by independents on the site itch.io, holding a 1.97% share.</text>
			<text lang="pl">LÖVE (lub Love2D) to otwarty, wieloplatformowy silnik do tworzenia gier wideo 2D. Silnik został napisany w języku C++ i używa Lua jako języka skryptowego. Jest opublikowany na licencji zlib.
API silnika umożliwia dostęp do funkcji obrazu i dźwięku hosta poprzez biblioteki SDL i OpenGL, a od wersji 0.10 także OpenGL ES 2 i 3. Czcionki mogą być renderowane przez silnik FreeType.
Zapewnia również podstawowe zarządzanie plikami w " sandboxie", aby uniknąć udostępniania całego swojego dysku wykonywanym grom.
W lipcu 2018 roku był to 10 najczęściej używany przez niezależnych graczy silnik gry w serwisie itch.io, z udziałem 1,97%.</text>
			<text lang="ru">Свободно распространяемый кроссплатформенный фреймворк (также известен как Love2D), предназначенный для разработки компьютерных игр на языке Lua. Распространяется по лицензии zlib, предусматривающей свободное использование как в открытых, так и в коммерческих проектах с закрытым исходным кодом.
LÖVE не является конструктором игр, ориентированным на новичков: фреймворк не имеет собственных средств разработки, а является лишь средой выполнения игр, написанных для этого движка. Для написания кода игры можно использовать любой текстовый редактор. Также в нём нет редактора уровней, все изображения, уровни и персонажи прописываются в коде игры.</text>
			<text lang="it">LÖVE (o Love2D) è un motore multipiattaforma open-source per lo sviluppo di videogiochi 2D. Il motore è scritto in C++ e utilizza Lua come linguaggio di scripting. È pubblicato sotto la licenza zlib.
L'API fornita dal motore consente l'accesso alle funzioni video e audio della macchina host attraverso le librerie SDL e OpenGL, o dalla versione 0.10 anche OpenGL ES 2 e 3. I caratteri possono essere resi dal motore FreeType.
Fornisce anche una gestione di base "sandbox" dei file per evitare di dare accesso a tutto il suo disco ai giochi eseguiti.
A luglio 2018, era il 10° motore di gioco più utilizzato dagli indipendenti sul sito itch.io, con una quota dell'1,97%.</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
