<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<text name="DataRilascio" extra="true">
			<text>1993</text>
		</text>
		<text name="Produttore" extra="true">
			<text>Creatonic/Videojet/Timlex</text>
		</text>
		<text name="nomesistema_nu" extra="true">
			<text>Mega Duck</text>
		</text>
		<text name="Descrizione" extra="true">
			<text>The Mega Duck was released by Creatronic, Videojet and Timlex in 1993 mainly in Germany and France. Looks alike a Game Boy with the monochrome green screen, it's "start", "Select", "A" and "B" buttons and directional pad but that's were the similiraties ends.
The carts are about 2 1/8 inchs by 2 1/2 inchs with 36 pins to connect with the cartridge slot of the Mega Duck (unlike the 32-pins of the Game Boy or the 40-pins of the Supervision).</text>
			<text lang="pl">Mega Duck został wydany przez Creatronic, Videojet i Timlex w 1993 roku głównie w Niemczech i Francji. Wygląda podobnie jak Game Boy z monochromatycznym zielonym ekranem, przyciskami "Start", "Select", "A" i "B" oraz klawiaturą kierunkową, ale na tym podobieństwa się kończą.
Carts są około 2 1/8 cala na 2 1/2 cala z 36 pinami, aby połączyć się z gniazdem kartridża Mega Duck (w przeciwieństwie do 32-pinów Game Boy lub 40-pinów Supervision).</text>
			<text lang="ru">Mega Duck был выпущен компаниями Creatronic, Videojet и Timlex в 1993 году в основном в Германии и Франции. Похож на Game Boy с монохромным зеленым экраном, кнопками "Start", "Select", "A" и "B" и джойстиком, но на этом сходство заканчивается.</text>
			<text lang="it">Il Mega Duck è stato distribuito da Creatronic, Videojet e Timlex nel 1993, principalmente in Germania e Francia. Assomiglia a un Game Boy con lo schermo verde monocromatico, i tasti "start", "Select", "A" e "B" e il pad direzionale, ma le somiglianze finiscono qui.
Le cartucce sono di circa 2,8 pollici per 2,5 pollici con 36 pin da collegare allo slot per cartucce del Mega Duck (a differenza dei 32 pin del Game Boy o dei 40 pin del Supervision).</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
