<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<text name="DataRilascio" extra="true">
			<text>2017</text>
		</text>
		<text name="nomesistema_nu" extra="true">
			<text>Pinball FX3</text>
		</text>
		<text name="Descrizione" extra="true">
			<text>Pinball FX 3 is a pinball simulator video game developed and published by Zen Studios and released for Microsoft Windows, Xbox One, PlayStation 4 in September 2017 and then released for the Nintendo Switch in December 2017.
Pinball FX 3 allows players to play one of several simulated pinball tables, and includes online scoreboard support for informal competition with other players. The game is aimed to provide a more engaging multiplayer experience than previous titles; the game will provide support for asynchronous competitive multiplayer options, and tournament-style play. There will be shared leaderboards and multiplayer options among platforms, although PlayStation 4 players can only compete with users playing through Steam on Windows due to Sony's initial decision to prohibit cross-platform play between its PlayStation 4 and other consoles.</text>
			<text lang="pl">Pinball FX 3 to symulator pinballu gra wideo opracowana i opublikowana przez Zen Studios i wydana dla Microsoft Windows, Xbox One, PlayStation 4 we wrześniu 2017 roku, a następnie wydana dla Nintendo Switch w grudniu 2017 roku.
Pinball FX 3 pozwala graczom grać w jeden z kilku symulowanych stołów pinballowych i zawiera wsparcie tablicy wyników online dla nieformalnej rywalizacji z innymi graczami. Gra ma na celu zapewnienie bardziej wciągającego doświadczenia wieloosobowego niż poprzednie tytuły; gra zapewni wsparcie dla asynchronicznych opcji konkurencyjnego multiplayera, a także gry w stylu turniejowym. Będą wspólne tablice liderów i opcje multiplayer między platformami, chociaż gracze PlayStation 4 mogą konkurować tylko z użytkownikami grającymi przez Steam na Windows ze względu na początkową decyzję Sony o zakazie gry międzyplatformowej między PlayStation 4 i innymi konsolami.</text>
			<text lang="ru">Cамая масштабная игра в пинбол, которая придется по душе всем поклонникам этой классической аркады. Многопользовательские соревнования, пользовательские турниры и игры лиги — у вас будут безграничные возможности для игры в пинбол.
Pinball FX3 включает обширную библиотеку столов, оформленных в стиле самых известных брендов, включая Aliens™,Family Guy, TellTale's The Walking Dead, Portal® и т. д.
- Давно не играли в пинбол? Pinball FX3 включает новый режим для одного игрока, где вы сможете вдоволь потренироваться!
- Все столы получили обновленную графику и дополнительные эффекты.
- Все столы включают новые игровые режимы, новые бонусы, дополнительные предметы и многое другое!</text>
			<text lang="it">Pinball FX 3 è un simulatore di flipper sviluppato e pubblicato da Zen Studios e pubblicato per Microsoft Windows, Xbox One, PlayStation 4 nel settembre 2017 e poi rilasciato per Nintendo Switch nel dicembre 2017.
Pinball FX 3 permette ai giocatori di giocare su uno dei diversi tavoli da flipper simulati e include il supporto del tabellone online per una competizione informale con altri giocatori. Il gioco mira a fornire un'esperienza multigiocatore più coinvolgente rispetto ai titoli precedenti; il gioco offre il supporto per le opzioni multigiocatore competitive asincrone e per il gioco in stile torneo. Le classifiche e le opzioni multigiocatore saranno condivise tra le varie piattaforme, anche se i giocatori di PlayStation 4 potranno competere solo con utenti che giocano tramite Steam su Windows, a causa della decisione iniziale di Sony di vietare il gioco multipiattaforma tra PlayStation 4 e altre console.</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
